

My Contact

simonaarsova92@gmail.com

(+389 75 382 008

Partizanski Odredi br. 155/1-12, Skopje

Hard Skill

- Editing
- Content management
- Gramma
- Research
- Project coordination

Soft Skill

- Teamwork and cooperation
- Reliability
- · Emotional intelligence
- Responsibility

Education Background

- IIK Berlin, Germany
 German intensive course
 Completed in 2018
- Faculty of Philology "Blazhe Koneski" Bachelor's degree in translation from English to Macedonian and vice versa and from German to Macedonian Completed in 2014
- School of foreign languages "Challenge"
 English Course
 Completed in 2009

SIMONA ARSOVA

Media Analyst

About Me

A hard-working person who is able to remain professional and calm in all circumstances. My greatest qualities are my research, communication, and writing skills. I have honed my skills through years of experience summarising German articles into English and German and mentoring new employees. Moreover, I have contributed to ensuring project success by meeting quality expectations.

Professional Experience

A Data Pro | Media/Senior Analyst with German/English 2018 – 2022

Key responsibilities:

- Screening media news stories about famous companies in English and German
- Writing summaries of German articles into English and German
- Content analysis
- Segment building
- Assisting in project training / projects for new employees
- Performing quality checks and providing feedback to junior analysts

Freelance SEO writer 2017 - 2018

Key responsibilities:

Web content in English: health and technology

Ars Studio Skopje | Translator 2015 – 2016

• Key responsibilities:

German to Macedonian translation of the books:

- 1. Die Krisis der europäischen Wissenschaften und die transzendentale Phänomenologie, Edmund Husserl (2012)
- 2.Das jugoslawische Makedonien 1918-1941. Eine Randregion zwischen Repression und Integration, Nada Boškovska (2009)
- 3.Das makedonische Jahrhundert Von den Anfängen der nationalrevolutionären Bewegung zum Abkommen von Ohrid 1893–2001, Stefan Troebst (2007)
- 4. Neue Wege der Ontologie, Nicolai Hartmann (2014)
- 5. Der philosophische Glaube, Karl Jaspers (2012)
- 6. Wahrheit und Methode Herausgegeben von Günter Figal Akademie Verlag Einbandabbildung: Hans-Georg Gadamer, (1999)